Hey everyone, thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. My name is
Jeremiah Kowski and on this podcast I
help coaches, mentors, and trainers
scale their businesses to make way more
money than they ever thought possible in
their life. And listen, I'd love to work
with you. If you're a coach, mentor,
trainer, and you want to work closely
with me inside of my Wealthy Coach
Academy program. And that's where I work
with you, come alongside you to help you
build everything out, help you sell
more, help you get more leads, and help
you make that money and impact people
because those are the most important
things is impacting people's lives and
creating transformation through your
coaching and mentoring. Now, in this
episode, I want to talk about how to use
chat GPT to create all of your ads in
your business.
And this is something that I've been
teaching people for a while, but I want
to just show you how we do this. Number
one, when you're creating an ad, you
want to make sure that
it it's going to connect with the right
person that you want to become your
client. The truth is, not everybody is
meant to be your client.
And oftentimes, I think people over
analyze the process of creating ads. I'm
not going to go over the process of the
ads manager or things like that, the
technical aspects of that. You can go
find that on YouTube. I got courses in
my program where I walk you through step
by step on how to do that. But I want to
show you how to create the ads, the
creatives, the graphics, all that. Put
all that together for what converts
really well and how chat GPT is actually
one of the best resources for this. It
starts with having an offer and a
landing page. And so an offer, landing
page is some kind of a page where you're
going to send people for them to sign up
for your offer. This is a landing page
right here for an offer right here. All
about building an evergreen business. Uh
we have a brand new one we're about to
launch real soon uh by the time of this
recording. It should be launched out
there all about getting more leads in
your business. I put this together. And
so the thing is is that an offer or a
landing page
describes what it is that you're
marketing to people. So if I'm going to
take this right here, this is going to
be a great example of this. I'm going to
take this and I'm going to bring this
into chat GPT. Now, we start with a
landing page like this. If you don't
have a landing page, my free AI prompts
that I have right over here on my
website. Free AI prompts at the top of
my website right here. You can see it
right there. If you're watching this on
YouTube, you can see the video of it.
It's right at the top of my website. It
has my top AI prompts. Anyways, if you
sign up, go check it out. There's a
Google doc right here. You can go
download and this will help you create
your ad copy. This will help you create
your landing page copy as well, sales
page copy. This will help you come up
with ideas for your marketing, for your
offer, for your coaching program, and
all those things out there. And so, this
is a invaluable resource to you to be
able to come up with sales copy for your
offers. So, once we have the sales copy
for our offer, like we have this uh this
evergreen offer right here with that
lead generation offer that we were
talking about.
Okay,
I'm going show you right here. Whack.
There we go. Leads. I'm going to copy
and paste this text right here right
into
chat JBT.
Okay. And I'm going to say this. Turn
the following
sales copy into PAS copy.
Make me four versions of PAS copy unique
angles.
That would be the foundation of an ad
campaign.
And then I'm just going to paste my
sales letter right there. And we're
going to see what this creates. Okay,
this is how I create all of my ads all
the time. It starts with this step. I
always start with this, okay? Stop
dancing for the algorithm. You're
grinding out your daily post. Never feel
forced to dance. Own your audience. Own
your income from scrolls to sales.
Secure the bag. $5 a day ads. Okay,
great. Now watch. Convert the above into
Facebook ads. Copy. Whether you're
running Instagram or Facebook ads, we're
going to do this this way. This also
works for Instagram ads.
I actually build everything out as an
Instagram base. for what we're doing.
Written copy plus headlines. Okay,
that's what we're going to do. We're
going to convert the above into Facebook
ads copy. And I'm using the chat GPT03
algorithm. I find this to be one of the
best uh for doing this. It's going to
create some great stuff like this. Sick
of filming reals, learning Tik Tok
trends, or writing vulnerable captions
for pity likes? Here's the truth. The
algorithm doesn't care if you succeed.
Your email list does. Grab my free
30-minute class to seal the 30 minute
subscriber system that pulls in
thousands of targeted leads every week.
Plug and play. This is exceptional. This
is just that like that is perfect sales
copy for an ad. I love it. It's perfect.
Let's see the next one. Borrowed
platforms equals borrowed income. One
policy tweak and your reach. Okay. This
one's not the best. Not a big fan of
this one. Okay. All right. From scrolls
to sales. Likes don't pay the bills, but
an email list filled with ideal clients
says, "That's a great headline." This is
killer sales copy right there. Join my
30-minute class and turn endless
scrolling into steady sales with simple
subscriber magnet that you can set up
before your next coffee is cold. That's
awesome. Want to capture thousand
subscri Yeah Yep. That's again, perfect
sales copy right here. Perfect. Okay.
Think you need a big budget to grow an
email list? Think again. All right. So
yeah, this is another great line of
sales copy. This is more the ads angle
right there. So if I'm running ads and
I'm going to be running ads for this
campaign, those are some versions of
this that I'll do. Now, for me
personally,
I would actually go through this process
like three or four more times and have
it generate me like 16 different
versions and really start to refine and
look at which ones are the best. Yeah,
I'm going to sit in front of chat GPT
and I'm going to have it generate me
four more. four more new concepts, new
ideas, because what it's then it's going
to do is I'm going to be able to take
those nuances and really bring them
together to piece something exceptional
together.
Next though, what I'm going to do is
this. I'm going to say great take the
above copy
and generate me 20 powerful
Facebook ads headlines that are
outcomebased.
Outcomebased is the key. And we'll use
maybe one or two of these headlines on
our ads. Headlines aren't that crazy
important.
Turn $5 ads into clients. Wake up new
subscribers.
from scrolls to sales fast.
Convert likes into revenue.
Get clients while you sleep. That's not
a bad one.
Email list equals predictable pay.
That's also a pretty good one. Okay, so
there we go. So now what we're going to
do is we're going to take these ads and
we're going to say this.
Now
switch
switch gears. I want you to generate me
a video ad script that I can record
some video ads.
Write me four different video ad scripts
that follow the following ad video
format.
And I have a prompt for this in my
document
because it's one of my favorites. Let's
see. Here we go. Video ad script right
here.
Okay.
Video ad script that follows this
format. Attention grabbing question. Who
you are? Sentence that tells them what
you offer. Called to action. All right.
Quick question. If you could stop
dancing for the algorithm, wake up to
thousands of ready to buy subscribers
every single week. What if you could? My
name's Jowski. The last 10 years, it's
the last 22 years. doesn't know my
credentials or anything. He's just
adding that in there. U my one my
clients six figure months all mastering
list building. This one's decent. Could
five bucks a day really get you a
thousand new email subscribers every
single week. Listen, I'm Jeremy Marowski
and I've been building
giant email lists for multi-million
dollar companies over the years. Yeah,
that's what I would do. What happens if
your income disappears? So again, these
aren't perfect, but this gives you some
ideas.
My team and I turn random scrollers into
booked solid calendars like the coach
from 200. Yeah. Okay. Decent. We're
going to try a couple other versions
here. We're going to we're going to
create a prompt high converting social
media post right here.
Okay. So, I'm going to use this prompt
to create me four versions with really
punchy text
for social media posts.
And then I might tell it shorten this or
make it more punchy.
I'm going to say shorten these and make
them even more punchy. I always do that
on this on this prompt.
Then we'll also try this outcomebased
one as well.
25K months easy profit flywheel. Double
your revenue by quarter's end.
Uh okay. So here's the problem. This is
starting to deviate away from our actual
offer
itself.
So what I want to do is I want to bring
it back in alignment.
Rewrite these based on the actual offer.
This is one thing that happens with chat
GBT. It starts to go off the rails from
your original offer.
So I just got to remind it of what we're
actually
offering.
And then it's going to start to write it
in alignment with those things. So if
you start to it's like this these these
this copy that it's writing is not even
related to like our offer. It's so
weird, right? So I'm going to tell it
rewrite these based on the actual offer.
Coaches and experts. Okay, we're going
to say this. So we're going to start
here.
We're going to go back. We're going to
do this.
50k months are calling. Pack your
pipeline till it bursts. Auto lead
engine. Double your revenue. Have to
stress.
Let's try this other outcomebased one
right here because that one's not giving
me copy that I would want. Let's try
this one.
Oh, yeah. This is way better.
These are way better. So, sometimes you
don't get what you want, but that's why
we have the different prompts that we
test out. I tell it shorten them and
make them more punchy. Let's see what
this creates. A little punchier.
50 cent Instagram ad leads. Think
Facebook ads in 2014. Cheap current
blueprint playbook. Turn $5 into thou I
would say thousands of leads. Zero ads,
2x sales. one real tic tac.
See,
it's not quite.
I wonder if I take this text and then I
give it my context text.
Context to write ads about. Sometimes I
got to do this. We'll put it in some
brackets. Context. Now, let's see what
this creates. And then we'll make it
punch here as well.
These are just some of my processes that
I use. There we go. Thousands of buyer
leads in 30 minutes. No goofy reels.
Person experts feel like 2014 cheap.
That's awesome. Let's shorten these and
make them punchier.
Just going to shorten these up.
There we go. Content equals crickets.
30-minute system plus $5 ads equals
buyers. So, there's some great ideas
that you could put. You could overlay
those over video. You could use some
B-roll video kind of like this. This is
the style that I would do for this. I
would do a style where you're like I
would overlay the text that it's
generating like this over a video of me
with my family or something like that.
Or I have some AI generated videos right
here. You can there's lots of concepts
that you could do to create different
stuff like that. And these ads actually
read really well online. They read
really well. Okay. Now, the last thing
I'm going to show you is how you can
also generate some concepts for uh image
ads. Okay. take all the above for this
offer and generate me 10 concepts for
image ads that I could create that tell
a story might be a little meme like
and
maybe even cartoonbased.
This is something I like to do cartoon
based meme like type image ads.
10 powerp packed. The algorithm hamster
wheel cartoon coach running out of giant
hamster wheels hashtags with a smug
little email list troll carrying cash.
Tired yet? Build a list, not blisters.
Free cash. Okay.
Generate me
image number one from the above.
And this is where what I can do is I can
take this and I can have this turn into
different ads. Buyer magnet magnetism.
Huge horseshoe magnet. Buyer magnet lead
magnet freebie hunter slide away.
Attract buyers not browsers.
Grab it. Okay.
Inbox raintorm coach opens an umbrella.
New subscriber emails. Let it pour
thousands of subs in 30 minutes. Count
me in.
So what chatt does is it can go ahead
and it can generate you some of these
ideas for uh image ads. I'm going to
show you a couple that we generated
recently for a client. Um, here's some
right here. Skip Dr. Google. Ask Sandy.
Sandy GPT right here. We just launched a
Sandy GPT.
Uh, here's another one right here. Stop
drowning in info. Start thriving. One
hub for clarity and confidence. So, this
is all generated with chat GPT based on
the concept of an offer that we were
promoting for a client over here for
this uh women's hormones group. which is
amazing. It's already brought in dozens
of clients in the last three days just
from testing this in this offer uh by
doing this. Listen, if you're a coach or
mentor and you want to work with me
together to build your business, I'd
love to do that. I'd love to chat with
you. You can talk with me on Instagram.
You can go check out the links below.
You can jump into my Wealthy Coach
Academy program and see how that all
works together and how we could work
together to build your business to
create the kind of life and income that
you want. I love seeing coaches and
mentors go from struggling trying to get
clients to finally making the kind of
money that they want to make online. And
and I can help you get there. I can hold
your hand, come alongside you and walk
you through the process. It's not
impossible when you know what to do and
you have the right mentor with you. And
I can be that for you with this. Okay,
so look, this is generating us that
image now. It's actually generating the
image that it came up with.
I'm really eager to see kind of how this
comes out. Oh, look at that. Build a
list, not blisters. Tired yet? Reals,
hashtags, trends. The guy in the email
list, he's making money. I love this.
This is like a great ad right there that
you could run.
Um, you could even say, "Generate me a
trendy meme
style ads that use uh popular
meme formats. So many memes are out
there. Memes work great for ads.
Um, this is another great way to
generate these. Can generate me 10 meme
style uh things.
Memes like Drake's Hotline. Bling
posting reels daily. 30 minute
subscriber system. Choose wisely. This
is great. Yep.
Buyer list and this content. Uh two
buttons. Sweaty coach. 10-hour content.
30-minute class.
Uh
to waking up. Oh, this one's good.
Generate me this ad.
Do the great Gatsby. Cheers. Uh, Leo
right there. Leo raising his glass
to waking up to new subscriber alert.
So, this is great. So, you can have this
generate this or you can go in um uh
meme
creator. Let's see. Gatsby Leo.
And this is the format right here with
Le Leonardo DiCaprio
right here on image flip meme generator.
You could actually generate
that meme that it gives us
right here on the image.
You put that as the top text to waking
up to new subscriber alerts.
One a morning like this comment cheers.
And that could like be our
ad right there. You can literally
download this, use it as an ad. Okay, so
those are just some great concepts that
you could do. Um, there is another tool
that's out there. It's a little bit more
expensive. Google Flow Studio.
Uh, whoops. Google Flow. Let me see.
With Google Flow, you could actually go
ahead and
generate incredible
videos. These are all AI generated
videos that you could use.
Um, and we and we went and generated
these for different things. You can
script them. You can put them together.
These you could actually even use these
for your ads. Put a few different videos
together by using this. It is expensive.
It's pricey to get access to the
highlevel uh version of this. Um,
the one that's really worth it. It's
about $250 a month. But my goodness, the
quality of the videos that you can
generate is incredible using V3 right
here.
Um, and we've done some fun ones that we
tested out that we played around with,
did some really cool concepts for some
clients for those. And those are all AI
generated videos that have audio and all
that in there that you could run as ads.
And I have chat GPT actually script them
out, come up with them. Same process
like we were doing over here. it's able
to script a lot of those out and come up
with those concepts for us. So that is
exactly how you can use chat GPT to help
you create your offers, your ads,
generate leads, and start to make the
kind of money that you want to make in
your business. Chat GPT is one of the
best tools that's out there. If you want
to know more about using AI, again, my
coaching program, the Wealth Coach
Academy program, can show you a lot
about how to use it, creating the kind
of money that you want to make in your
business. Also, my YouTube channel, I
got some incredible videos that you can
watch that can walk you through step by
step all the different processes of
doing this. Oh, this is cool. It created
a a cartoon version of the Leo meme. I
love that. Super cool. So, it kind of
stands out right there to waking up to
new subscriber alerts.
Cheers. I love this. This is awesome.
Very cool. Listen, thanks for listening.
If you like this episode, share it with
somebody. Don't keep it to yourself.
Grow your life, everybody. We'll talk
soon. Have a good one.
[Applause]
[Music]